嘿 布巴 是我 福雷斯甘
Hey, Bubba. It's me, Forrest Gump.
我记得你说过的话
I remember everything you said,
我已经安排好了
and I got it all figured out.
我带来两万四千五百六十二块四毛七分
I'm taking $24,562.47
这是我所有的钱
that I got, that's left
其它钱用来理发和买新衣服
after a new hair cut and a new suit
还有带妈妈上街吃了一顿好饭
and took Mama out to a real fancy dinner,
还买了车票 还买了三瓶汽水
and I bought a bus ticket, then three Dr. Peppers.
告诉我
Tell me something.
你是傻瓜吗？
Are you stupid or something?
做傻事的才是傻瓜 先生
Stupid is as stupid does, sir.
我拿到这些钱是因为我说：
That's what's left after me saying,
“我和全美乒乓球队在中国时
"When I was in China on the all-America Ping-Pong team,
“我最喜欢打乒乓球…
"I just loved playing Ping-Pong
“用我的菲利奥莱乒乓球拍”
with my Flex-O-Lite Ping-Pong paddle,"
谁都知道这不是真话
which everybody knows isn't true,
但妈妈说它只是一个善意的谎话
but Mama said it was just a little white lie,
它不会伤害任何人
so it wasn't hurting nobody.
总之 剩下的钱我全部用来
So anyway, I'm putting all that
买燃料、绳索和网具
on gas, ropes, and new nets
以及一条全新的捕虾船
and a brand-new shrimping boat.